You've had stomach pain for so long.
你胃疼这么长时间
Why didn't you come in for a checkup earlier?
早点儿不来做检查
This is very dangerous.
这样很危险的
Once the test results come out,
等检查报告出来了
you must be hospitalized.
一定要住院啊
It's an old problem.
老毛病了
I'll be fine.
没事的
(Jiaojiao's project)
（娇娇的项目）
(is at a critical stage.)
（正在关键时期）
(Even if it costs me my life,)
（就算拼上这条命）
(I have to help her win it.)
（我也要帮她拿下）
Youhua, come work for us
佑华 你跳槽到我们
at Wayne Design.
维恩设计吧
Two months from now,
两个月后的
at the Paris Architecture Design Expo,
巴黎建筑设计展
I'll make you the lead designer.
我让你做主设计
I'll let the whole world witness
让全世界见证你
the debut of this mysterious design master.
这个神秘设计大师的亮相
Shiyi.
诗怡
I won't switch jobs.
我不会跳槽的
Jiaojiao and I are getting married soon.
我和娇娇马上就要结婚了
Her career
她的事业
is my career.
就是我的事业
Then I can only wish you both well.
那我就只能祝福你们啦
If you regret it,
你要是后悔了
remember to come find me.
记得找我呀
I'm not talking about the job switch.
我说的的不是跳槽
I'm talking about the marriage.
是结婚呦
Jiaojiao.
娇娇
You're carrying Youping's child now.
你现在怀着佑平的孩子
You need to take good care of yourself.
要好好的养胎
As for work,
这工作上的事
leave it to Youhua.
就交给佑华去做
Let my brother handle all the design plans.
设计方案都交给我哥做
You just focus on the baby.
你就安心养胎
Okay. I'll listen to you.
好 都听你的
Jiaojiao.
娇娇
What is going on?
这是怎么回事
We're getting married next week,
我们下周就要结婚了
and you're pregnant with my brother's child?
你怀了我弟弟的孩子
Brother.
哥
Why are you here?
你怎么来了？
You aren't following my sister-in-law, are you?
你不会是在跟踪嫂子吧？
I'm here about my stomach illness.
我是来看胃病
I didn't expect to catch you two doing this.
没想到撞破你们的好事
Youhua.
佑华
Don't think so filthily.
你不要想得这么龌龊
Youping and I are innocent.
我和佑平是清白的
You're already pregnant with his child,
你都怀了他的孩子了
and you still have the nerve to say you're innocent?
还好意思说是清白的
Youhua.
佑华
Youping and I used artificial insemination.
我和佑平是人工受孕
Back then,
当初
he was taking stomach medicine to you.
他也是为了给你送胃药
That's why he had the accident.
所以才出的车祸
Now he can only sit in a wheelchair.
如今只能在轮椅上
Besides me,
除了我
who else would carry on his family line?
还有谁会给他传宗接代呀？
Doing this
这么做
is also for your Song family.
也是为了你们老宋家
You're marrying me,
和我结婚
but having my brother's child?
却帮我弟弟生孩子
Listen to what you're saying!
你听听自己在说什么！
Song Youhua.
宋佑华
I'm giving your brother an heir,
我帮你弟弟留个后
and you still criticize me.
你都要说三道四
How can I
你让我以后
trust myself to you in the future?
怎么才放心把自己交给你
Your brother will have an heir.
你弟弟有后了
Aren't you happy?
那你不高兴吗？
You're even holding him back.
还拖他的后腿
What kind of brother are you?
有你这样当哥哥的吗？
Pretending. Pretending to be sick again.
装 又在装病
If it weren't for you,
要不是因为你
Youping
佑平
wouldn't have become disabled.
也不会落个残疾
Mom.
妈
Sister-in-law.
嫂子
Don't argue with Brother.
你们别和哥吵
This is all my fault.
这事都怪我
I'm useless.
是我不中用
I became disabled.
成了残废
I dragged the whole family down.
拖累了整个家
Look at Youping,
你看看佑平
then look at yourself.
再看看你
You're both my sons.
都是我儿子
How can there be such a big difference?
怎么差距就这么大呢？
I'm telling you,
我告诉你啊
within three days,
三日内
move out of the wedding house.
搬出婚房
Jiaojiao needs to rest during pregnancy.
娇娇要去养胎
Youping and I
我和佑平
will go take care of her.
要去服侍她
If you delay me from holding my eldest grandson,
你要耽误我抱大孙子
then you're no son of mine.
你就不是我儿子
Let's go.
我们走
Zhang Shiyi, let's get married.
张诗怡 我们结婚吧
Really? You've finally made up your mind?
真的 你终于想清楚了
I'll book a flight home right now.
我现在就订回国的机票
You can't go back on it.
你可不许反悔
Next week, at the Civil Affairs Bureau.
下周 民政局见
Hubby.
老公
Mwah.
么么哒